<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="86868" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Real Life" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="This mod allows you to configure the age that cims move from one life stage to the other." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
This mod has a few options to configure the age that cims move from one life stage to the other. It also has options to configure their education.

## Age Settings

This setting menu allows you to configure some age settings:

* **Child School Start Age:** The age that children will start going to Elementary School.
* **Child Age Limit:** The age that children will become teenagers.
* **Teen Age Limit:** The age that teenagers will become adults.
* **Adult Retirement Age:** The age that adults will retire and become elderly.
* **Female Life Expectancy:** The average age that women are likely to die.
* **Male Life Expectancy:** The average age that men are likely to die.

## Education Settings

This section has a few options to configure education:

* **University Capacity for College:** Allows college students to go for a college degree in an Univeristy. This feature is not set by default. The percentage of University capacity that will be for College degrees can be set in this option. Values higher than zero will enable this feature and also decrease the number of available spots for Univeristy students.
* **Number of years in College:** The number of years that cims will stay in College.
* **Number of years in University:** The number of years that cims will stay in University.
* **Elementary School Graduation Probability:** The probability that a citizen will graduate elementary school.
* **High School Graduation Probability:** The probability that a citizen will graduate high school.
* **College Graduation Probability:** The probability that a citizen will graduate college.
* **University Graduation Probability:** The probability that a citizen will graduate university.
* **Entering High School Probability:** The probability that a citizen will enter High School.
* **Adult Entering High School Probability:** The probability that an adult will enter High School.
* **Worker Continue Education Probability:** The probability that a worker will continue their education.

## Birth and Relationship Settings

This section has a few options to adjust the game birth and relationship parameters. These are factors which you can use to increase or decrease the original value. These are factors that can be adjusted:

* Student Birth Rate
* Base Birth Rate
* Adult Female Birth Rate Bonus
* Divorce Rate
* Look for Partner Rate

**WARNING:** Using this mod in an existing city may cause a death wave.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/menu1.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/menu2.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/real-life-mod.1698231/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.7.3" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<ChangeLog>
* Updated for version 1.2.5f1
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/ruzbeh0/RealLife" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.com/channels/1024242828114673724/1270106414337097868" />
	<ExternalLink Type="paypal" Url="https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/ruzbeh0" />
	<ExternalLink Type="kofi" Url="https://ko-fi.com/ruzbeh0" />
</Publish>
